(Sheldon:)What has that vixen done to me,
Leonard?
(Sheldon:)How do I make it stop?
(Leonard:)Well, if you had a physical relationship,
l'd say propose during sex.
Turns out that's a real mood-killer.
- l assume we're talking about you now?
- Yeah.
(Sheldon:)So that's how this works?
l complain and then you complain...
(Sheldon:)...and no one offers any solutions?
(Leonard:)Pretty much.
(Sheldon:)Well, no wonder the women
are winning.
(Howard:)Mr. Rostenkowski, are you busy?
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)Just looking at some old pictures.
Come on in.
Family pictures, or?...
Holy crap, that's a dead person.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)Last murder case before I retired.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)How many bodies do you see there?
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)Careful. It's a trick question.
- I'm not sure.
- No, you'll never get it. It's a fraction.
How about that, heh.